# **Igor Semenkov**

- Dnipro
- +38 (050) 480-38-46
- semenkov.box@gmail.com
- LinkedIn **Igor Semenkov**
- Портфолио GitHub



## **Summary**

I have a work experience both in large companies (banking) and in the private business. Being the director of a small company for the last 5 years, I came to the conclusion that the main thing in any profession is cooperation and effective interaction with people.

I approach work with responsibility, following deadlines and with precision in details. I'm not afraid of difficulties and I always bring what I started to the end.

I have a great desire to work in a company where there are opportunities for professional and intellectual development.

### **Professional Skills**

- 1) HTML5 / CSS3;
- 2) JavaScript, jQuery, jQuery-UI;
- 3) Gulp / Webpack;
- 4) Bootstrap;
- 5) MVC

## Language skills

English – Pre-Intermediate

## **Experience**

1) September 2015 - May 2020.

LLC "BSK Trade". Position - director.

Main tasks: implementation of the company's strategic and tactical plans; expansion of the sales market and growth of the company as a whole; staff recruitment; setting tasks and managing production, warehouse and logistics of the company.

2) July 2013 - September 2015.

PE "Maximum". Position - Sales Manager.

Main tasks: negotiating, expanding the sales market and providing services to the company

#### **Education**

1) National Metallurgical Academy of Ukraine (NMetAU)
Economy and Management faculty

Specialization – International business administration (2008-2010).

2) National Metallurgical Academy of Ukraine (NMetAU) Electrometallurgical Faculty. Specialization – Special metallurgy (2001-2006).

#### **Additional Education, Courses**

- 1) Course Front-End Basic Hillel
- 2) Course Front-End Pro Hillel